challenger.com.sg 2019-07-19

# Challenger Technologies Limited

**Help  us create a better Challenger shopping environment.**

In order to create a better Challenger, we need your help. You can help by providing us with various kinds of information to help us serve you better, and ultimately improve Challenger for everyone. Below you'll find an explanation of some of the reasons we request information from you, as well as some details about how we obtain and use that information. Throughout this Privacy Policy, where we refer to your "personal information" means any information you provide to us about you. This includes your national registration identity card (NRIC) number, foreign identification number (FIN), passport number, name, postal address, email address, date of birth and telephone number.

**Where we collect your personal information:**

_Customer relations_

In order for a customer relations representative to respond to your questions or concerns, we may need personal information such as your name, ValueClub ID, email, ValueClub ID, email address and telephone number. This information is used to answer your questions as completely and thoroughly as possible.

_Membership_

When you sign up or renew a ValueClub membership, we use the particulars you provide to ensure you enjoy the full membership benefits and keep you up to date with important membership announcement. These may include an easy way to identify yourself at any Challenger store and for secured access to Hachi.tech marketplace, where members enjoy member discounts, promotions and rebate redemption.

_Contest_

When you participate in a contest, we may ask for personal information in order for us to identify and verify the winner of our contest. Regardless the reasons we collect your personal information for, we promise only to use it in the ways set out in this Privacy Policy. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to us processing this personal information in one or more ways described in this Privacy Policy.

 _Information that we collect automatically:_

Many web surfers are concerned about their privacy and the use of "cookies" on the Internet. Cookies are small files that can be used to store information you have already provided. Cookies cannot be used to "steal" information about you or your computer system. The Challenger website uses cookies to remember your preferences. For example, the website may remember which page you viewed, to make your next visit more convenient. Nevertheless, cookies can be disabled in your web browser's Internet Options.

_Point of Sale_

We request non-members who opt for an eReceipt to provide an email address for us to deliver the transaction receipt to. This email address will be used solely for transactional purpose only.

**What we will do with your information:**

Challenger does not sell your personal information to third parties.

Occasionally, we do need to hire other companies to help us provide some services such as marketing assistance. We’ll limit the personal information we give them, and they will only have access to your personal information for the purposes of performing such functions. They are strictly monitored by Challenger in order to make certain our customers' privacy is always protected.

_Facilitate ValueClub membership benefits_

The personal data you provide to us will enable us to (a) track your purchase records, (b) allocate rebates according to your purchase records, (c) update you periodically about relevant programs through which you may earn  rebates or enjoy member benefits, (d) redeem your rebates when you shop with participating merchants, (e) update our profiling of customer preferences so that we may be able to serve you better, and; (f) provide you seamless access to Hachi.tech, our partnered online Tech marketplace.

_Marketing_

If you provide any personal information to us, you give us permission to contact you for marketing purposes, which may include messages via post, telephone, SMS or email.

The information you provide will enable us to (a) track your purchase records, (b) allocate rebates according to your purchase records, (c) update you periodically about relevant programs through which you may earn rebates, and; (d) update our profiling of customer preferences so that we may be able to serve you better.

We will ensure that we only send you messages that we think will be of interest to you - for instance, the dates of our in-store sales, details of special offers or information about new products and services. If you do not want us to use your personal information to market to you, you can decide to opt-out of these types of marketing messages at any time by changing the settings in your Profile or by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email we send to you.

**Storing your information and keeping it up to date:**

_Out of sight, but never out of reach  _

When you share your personal information with Challenger, you will always have access to this information. Where you store a "Profile" on the website, you can amend the selected details stored in your account yourself. Alternatively, you can update, change, or remove any personal contact information & residential address at any time by calling, writing, or emailing us using any of the options provided.  

_Keeping it safe_

We are committed to providing appropriate security controls to protect your personal information against foreseeable hazards. Making sure that your personal information is secure is very important to Challenger.  

**Change of address? Change of personal information? Let us know:**

As a ValueClub member, you can also log in to update your contact number or addresses any time. If you would like us to update your personal information, remove your name from our mailing list, or if you have any questions about Challenger’s privacy policies or your personal information, simply contact us through our online request form [here](https://challenger.zendesk.com/hc/en-us) or email us at valueclub(at)challenger.sg.

We will respond to your questions or concerns within 3 working days.

Occasionally, we may decide to change this Privacy Policy so we suggest that you review it periodically so you will be aware of any changes.

 _By using this site, you consent to the above privacy policies._
